# Juhwan Lee

Cell: 360-593-6736 • ljh1230vvv@gmail.com • juhwan@pdx.edu • https://www.linkedin.com/in/juhwan-lee/ • https://github.com/juroc95

### **ABOUT**

Enthusiastic software engineer with extensive technical experience in software testing and full-stack web development in a professional team environment. Familiar with data structures, object-oriented programming, systems programming, algorithms, and relational databases. Successfully work in teams and self-directed settings with the ability to quickly learn and master new technologies.

### **EDUCATION**

#### PORTLAND STATE UNIVERSITY

Portland, Oregon

### **Expected Graduation: Mar 2023**

**Bachelor of Science in Computer Science** 

Overall GPA: 3.55 / 4.00

- Activities and societies: Software Engineering Capstone Team Lead
- Academic honors: President's List (Winter 2022), Dean's List (Spring 2022), International Achievement Scholarships (\$12,000)
- Relevant courses: Data Structures, Object-Oriented Programming, Systems Programming, Software Engineering, Operating Systems, Algorithms and Complexity, Relational Databases, Web Development

### **SKILLS**

Technologies: C, C++, Python, Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, HTML, CSS, SQL, Node.js, Linux, Vim, VScode, Git Languages: Native in Korean, Fluent in English

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**FASOO** 

Seoul, South Korea

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

- Software Engineer Intern Worked as part of a four-member team under the Wrapsody Development team for the internship project called Wrapsody eCo Workspace
  - Designed and implemented a new collaborative workspace, where users can freely share their opinions, within Wrapsody eCo by integrating a real-time open-source collaborative text editor called Etherpad
  - Presented Wrapsody eCo Workspace in front of the CEO, team leaders, and senior developers on the last day of the internship

## **MEDIAZEN** Software Engineer Intern

Seoul, South Korea Jun 2021 - Sep 2021

Suggested new application ideas for STT, TTS, NLU, and Computer Vision in front of the team leader and senior developers on the first

- Created 1000 test scenarios for the advancement of ART (Automatic Recognition Test), a software testing automation tool
- Responsible for software testing of the Volkswagen Voice Control System and reporting test results to the project manager when a new version is released

### **REPUBLIC OF KOREA NAVY**

Gyeryong, South Korea Jan 2018 - Oct 2019

## Petty Officer Second Class, Administrative Clerk

week of the internship

- In charge of reporting the personnel status of the FF-956 to the fleet, flotilla, and squadron
- Assisted in administrative work in the secretary's office of the vice chief of naval operations

## **PROJECTS**

## **WALKTOBER**

## Portland State University CS Capstone Project

Oct 2022 - Mar 2023

- Develop a cross-platform fitness challenge app called Walktober that is integrated with built-in iOS and Android fitness tracking systems by using TypeScript, Node.js, React, Ionic Framework, and Firebase
- Users can create an account, create or join a team, track their steps, interact with the participants, view the leaderboard for the event and for their team, and view event-wide announcements

## **TIKTIK APP**

## Side Project

Aug 2022 - Sep 2022

- Built a TikTok Clone Application using TypeScript, Next.js, React, and Sanity by following JavaScript Mastery Tutorial
- This TikTok Clone Application includes Google Auth, the ability to upload, publish, share, comment on, and like the videos; filtering by categories and advanced search functionalities, profile pages, suggested accounts, custom responsive design, and much more

## WRAPSODY ECO WORKSPACE

# Fasoo Internship Project

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

- Designed and implemented a new collaborative workspace, where users can freely share their opinions, within Wrapsody eCo by integrating a real-time open-source collaborative text editor called Etherpad
- Wrapsody eCo users can now freely share their opinions with their team members without having to move to the different platform

### **FULL STACK REALTIME CHAT MESSAGING APP**

#### Portland State University CS300 Project

Jan 2022 - Mar 2022

- Created a custom chat application using JavaScript, Node.js, React, and Stream by following JavaScript Mastery Tutorial
- This chat application includes direct and group chats, emojis & reactions, built-in gif support, the ability to edit & delete messages, specialized commands, and much more